[
    {
        "question": "Javascript is a(n) _______ language?",
        "choices": ["Object-Oriented","Object-Based","Procedural","None of the above"],
        "answer": "Object-Oriented",
        "progress": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?",
        "choices": ["var","let","Both A and B", "None of the above"],
        "answer": "Both A and B",
        "progress": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following methods is used to access HTML elements using Javascript?",
        "choices": ["getElementById()","getElementsByClassName()","Both A and B","None of the above"],
        "answer": "Both A and B",
        "progress": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "Upon encountering empty statements, what does the Javascript Interpreter do?",
        "choices": ["Throws an error","Ignores the statements","Gives a warning","None of the above"],
        "answer": "Ignores the statements",
        "progress": 40
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following methods can be used to display data in some form using Javascript?",
        "choices": ["document.write()","console.log()","window.alert()","All of the above"],
        "answer": "All of the above",
        "progress": 50
    },
    {
        "question": "How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?",
        "choices": ["const","var","let","constant"],
        "answer": "const",
        "progress": 60
    },
    {
        "question": "What keyword is used to check whether a given property is valid or not?",
        "choices": ["in","is in","exists","lies"],
        "answer": "in",
        "progress": 70
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the use of the <noscript> tag in Javascript?",
        "choices": ["The contents are displayed by non-JS-based browsers","Clears all the cookies and cache","Both A and B","None of the above"],
        "answer": "The contents are displayed by non-JS-based browsers",
        "progress": 80
    },
    {
        "question": "When an operator's value is NULL, the typeof returned by the unary operator is:",
        "choices": ["Boolean","Undefined","Object","Integer"],
        "answer": "Object",
        "progress": 90
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the Javascript “debugger” statement do?",
        "choices": ["It will debug all the errors in the program at runtime","It acts as a breakpoint in the program","It will debug the error in the current statement if any","All of the above"],
        "answer": "It acts as a breakpoint in the program",
        "progress": 95
    }
]